Hallo! The stakes are about to start!
This time, we'll be talking about Morning Musume。 This time I'll be talking with Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda and Riai Matsunaga from Juice-Juice,
Riai Matsunaga from Juice-Juice.
They will be presenting this time, so please bear with me until the end.
Project's 25th anniversary new member audition is now underway.
Yes, I know, I know, I know, I know.
Hiyama, do you remember anything about the audition?
I was in elementary school when I auditioned, so I was really just a kid,
That's why I had nothing to be afraid of, so I was able to go in with an open mind.
I was also a person of various types who auditioned with an open attitude,
If you are still wondering whether you should apply or not, please do so, because I think it will change your life,
We are looking forward to working with you.
Project2023 Summer City Circuit is now being held.
Morning Musume。 23 will be in Hiroshima on August 11, and Juice- Juice will be in Shinjuku Park on August 19.
Is there anything that has been enhanced for this encore tour?
Even though it is an encore tour, I don't want to show you exactly the same thing,
So, I don't want to show you exactly the same performance, setlist, new members, etc,
I think we will be able to show you a fresher performance, setlist, new members, etc. than the spring tour.
Juice-Juice had the Brokan Park in May,
We received a lot of comments that the performance was wonderful there,
I hope we can live up to their expectations and exceed them,
I would like to do my best in the summer as well.
We are looking forward to seeing you soon.
In addition, Morning Musume。 23 will release an album called Morning Musume。 25 Selection The 25th Anniversary album will be released on August 30.
Usually a best album is a compilation of singles, but we are going to release an album called "Morning Musume,Usually a best-of album is a compilation of singles,
This time, we are re-singing selected singles from the past 25 years.
It will be a kind of undiluted member version,
Of course, there will be a new album as well, so I hope you will enjoy it.
Please take a look at this video first.
Go ahead!
Into the world of Japanese albums
Thank you for watching!
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
Because I love you
Midnight sneak away
I've been a bad girl
I've lived my whole life as an innocent child
And that's my punishment
I've changed since I met you.
I miss you at all times.
Not because I'm a failure... but because I'm a woman.
Tell me you've become more attractive.
I've been trying to figure out what it's like to be in love.
But I can't stop the feelings I'm having.
I'm sorry I pulled the box today.
It's the only time I can do it.
I'm just trying to forget how much I love you.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I don't know what I'll do when you realize how much I love youI don't know what I'll do if you find out I love you.
I love you too much.
Ah, important cocoon.
I told you that love is all but over.
Have you ever been madly in love with someone?
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I love you all.
You won't regret it. It's my love.
It's my love.
Thanks for watching.
Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda and
Ria Matsunaga of Juice-Juice. STE!
From here, I would like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
I understand.
Ria Matsunaga, whose birthday was last month!
How do you want to spend your 18th year?
I want to spend it calmly.
Ai Matsunaga, who wrote a song with Ichika Arisawa, what kind of song did you write? A wonderful song!
What are you looking forward to the most this summer? Taking a bite of ice cream
What kind of idols do you like? Idols who like to sing
What is the best thing about Juice-Juice right now?
Thank you... the music... great songs... details...
Yes, in detail.
I composed the music, and Ichika Arisawa arranged it, and since I'm a person who hasn't studied any theory...I composed the music and Kazuka Arisawa arranged it.
I am a person who has not studied theory at all, so I really rely on my own senses to compose all the songs.
Do you like to have a lot of sounds in your compositions or do you like to have a lot of sounds in your compositions?
I like a lot of sounds. Ichika-chan analyzed my brain and gave me the idea that this is the kind of sound I want.
I think it's great that you were able to create this song.
It's fun. I'd love to write a song.
And I have a question for you. What kind of idols do you like?
Yes, idols who love to sing.
I think idols who are serious about singing are really cool.
I'm so happy to hear that.
I'm glad to hear that. Thank you very much.
The question for Ms. Oda will come after the VTR.
Hello! Stage.
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't.
I won't kiss you okay.
Even you couldn't take it away from me
CHOOSE CHOOSE PRIDE BRIDE NOW ON SALE
Oh Let's Play Lovely Music
Let's Dance Disco till morning Let's
CHOOSE CHOOSE FUNKY FLASHING NOW ON SALE
Is it because of the summer? Is it a dream?
A little unstable
Whose fault is it?
Ochanoma New Single
Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer on sale now!A Little Emotionally Unstable Summer on Sale
wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan tea horse
Zatcha Zatcha Zatcha Zatcha Zatcha Mahaloba
Ochanoma New Single
Ochanoma Mahaloba Ikaenova
Shake Ena, The Power to Believe in Yourself
Ordinary but Prohibited Unreasonable Dan Dan
Ocha no Ma New Single
Shekenare Now on sale
Yoritori midori midori, I can't choose one
Tape Tokimei Jana
Pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka pampaka
Ocha no Ma New Single
Yorotorimidori on sale now!
Hallo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask a question to Mr. Oda.
Yes, please.
The other day, she released her first photo essay,
Sakura and the Cat.
What kind of a person are you in this book?
It's very private.
This weekend you will perform at the Rock in Japan Festival 2023.
What are you working on for the outdoor stage under the scorching sun?
It is to spend time with the temperature outside. Everyday life.It is to spend the day with the temperature outside. Everyday life.
Mr. Oda says he is very particular about food.
What is the perfect food for this hot season?
A mixture of molokheiya, baby sardines, and natto (fermented soybeans).
What do you think about during a performance?I am either reflecting on my performance or thinking about the audience.
It's been about 3 months since the announcement of the new members.
How would you describe your role in Morning Musume。 In one word, how would you describe your role in Morning Musume。
Boss.
Wow! Thank you very much.
Have you been reflecting on your performance the whole time?
I'm reflecting on everything.
I'm reflecting on my singing, my dancing, my facial expressions, the way my hair moves, everything,
I don't do it in such a negative way,
I'm just looking at the faces of the audience,
I wonder if I have done something today, if I am happy,
I want them to think about what they did today, whether they are happy, and whether they will be able to live with that tomorrow,
I feel like I'm doing that to the clients, and I'm often reflecting on myself.
Amazing.
And now, I am a member of Morning Musume。 Your role in Morning Musume。
Yes, that's right.
There are older members who are like older sisters, and they are there for you in your private life,
There are people who are there for you on a personal level, too,
But we are all workmates, and we are doing what we do for the purpose of making good products,
But we are all colleagues in our work, and our purpose is to make good products,It is much closer to private life, like the 15th term,
Erio Sakura and others,
I am just a senior member of Morning Musume。 I am just a senior member of Morning Musume,
I would like to teach them about work.
She's cool. That's great. I learned a lot from this question.
I'm glad.
Yes, I'm glad. So, Halo! Ste. We'll continue after this.
Hello! STE.
Project's 25th anniversary special program.
What a surprise, that person will appear on the stage of "Halo! Project's 25th anniversary with the senior members.
Actually, I am also on the show.
Please take a look at the VTR. Please watch the VTR.
Project 25th Anniversary!
Project 25th Anniversary! Sta.
The three of us had a heated discussion about Tsunku III's songs in the recently released mook book of Tsunku III.
Project's mook book, and this time we would like to present an even more special version of that discussion.
We received a copy of the book today.
Here it is.
Thank you very much.
In addition to the three of us, we have a special guest this time.
This is him.
Ta-da!
This is ZUNK. Please give my regards to Mr. Zunku.
It's been a while.
How long has it been? I mean...,How long has it been? I mean,
I think it's different for everyone.
I think it has been since the breakup of ℃-ute.
I have been in contact with them, but I haven't met them properly,
Saitama is probably the last time.
I see. That was quite a while ago.
I've been watching you guys a little bit,
I don't feel like it.
I'm glad.
I saw the video of Miyamoto serving as a judge,
Oh my God!
I feel like there was something there.
I feel like there was, but I never got to meet them in person.
Even when ℃-ute broke up, I don't think we met each other.
We may have passed each other in passing, but that's about it,
I think it was a really long time ago.
So, to commemorate the 25th anniversary of Hello!
Project's 25th anniversary, I would like to talk about various things with these four of us.
Please bear with us until the end.
In the book, we talked a lot about Tsunku III's songs,
This time, I would like to ask about the three of us from Tsunku III's point of view.
I want to ask you, but I don't want to.
I feel like you guys know more about my work than I do.
That may be so.
You are already fans. I've already gone around twice.You're already a fan. I've already gone around twice.
I listened to the interview the other day in great detail and thought it was amazing.
I'm embarrassed.
Please be gentle today.
To be honest, I was getting excited because you weren't here.
Really? Today.
I had so many questions I wanted to ask you, but I couldn't meet you,
I've been feeling that it's difficult to ask you because we don't get to see each other very often, and I've been away from you for a long time,
What about this? What about that? What about that? I was like a selfish child.
Like a selfish child.
I could listen to them for a week or so.
That's how I feel.
A week.
A week from Hollywood.
But when did you guys study music so much?
After you graduated from Halo Pro?
I was wondering the same thing about you two.
They were talking about composition and chord progressions,
I thought that there were not so many aspects of Halo Project.
I think you probably know more about mathematical chord progressions than I do,
I had already studied the lyrics,
I have already studied the lyrics, or rather, the songs Tsunku III gave me are embedded in my DNA,
I feel like I've reached the age where I can analyze them.
It's like my vocabulary has caught up with me.
It's like I'm looking back on my life once more. I am.I feel like I have just looked back at my life once more. I am.
At what age did you start reading the lyrics again?
But actually, I didn't really start reading the lyrics again until after we broke up.
When I was working on the songs, I was singing the lyrics based on what I was feeling at the time,
But as I grew older, I began to understand the meaning of the old songs more,
But as an adult, I can understand the meaning of the old songs better, and when I sing them again, I can sing them with a completely different feeling.
I wish I had sung it that way back then.
But I still reread the songs at that time as well,
There were a lot of songs about jealousy and revenge over lost love, but the boundaries of imagination were too narrow for elementary school students,
But the boundaries of my imagination were too narrow for an elementary school student,
I was doing everything I could at the time,
As an adult, I feel like I have become more human.
But I don't think that such feelings would have made the song as energetic as it was,
If they were included.
There are probably some good qualities that are not included,
I was looking back on it, wondering if Tsunku III was also making it. I was looking back on the past.
Is that not true?
That's why I tell everyone these days not to put emotion into their songs.
I think the same about acting.
I think this a lot.
I think singing, acting, and TV dramas are different,
But in real life, do you ever hear someone tell you that they love you?
What are you asking?
What are you listening to on Halo! What are you listening to on Halo!
I don't think so.I don't think so.
Putting emotion into a performance means acting,
It suddenly becomes unnatural.
So, I'm not talking about what I said before,
I think it's just like when you're a little kid and you're singing along for no reason at all.
Ron.
The great sense of conviction is so compelling that the whole dialogue ends here.
But the sense of conviction is amazing.
I feel like it's all there, the goodness of idols.
In the end, it's the most lie-free thing.
That is the state of being.
There are many examples, but I remember when Berryz KOBO, Q, and BerryQ performed at Yokohama Arena, and at the end of the pre-show rehearsal, Tsunku♡ took the center stage and said, "I'm going to do it again.
Tsunku♡ gathered us all together on the center stage and explained to us one more time how to beat 16 beats, and since we were BerryQ, we had grown up quite a bit.
He said that the rhythm was still a little bit too soft. He said, "This is what that 16 beats really means! So Mr. TSUNKU♡ walked on the edge of the center stage himself.
He said, "It's a matter of course to lift your heels, and if you want, you should lift your heels 3mm off the floor.
It looks floating, doesn't it? I thought I was floating,
I thought it was not floating, but now I realize that there are no 16 beats in Hello!
I feel that when someone covers a Hello!
That's very impressive. I think it's like a gundam.
It floats.
I thought it was Doraemon.
I'm going to talk here, but I'm sorry if this turns into a sermon.
Yes, I'm used to it. I'm used to it. For 20 years, I've been told about rhythm.
Oda and Suzuki, if you let your guard down, it will come.
Prepare for the impact.Prepare for impact.
It's a D.
You're switching to an easy beat.
You've been telling me this for a long time, me too.
Laughing so hard. Laugh and follow through with your convictions.
I know a lot of girls are good singers to begin with, but they're so good that it just flows easily,
But I'm still following the order.
I was like, "Don't go up.
All the way up. I definitely spent all the way up to the venue.
I'm sorry.
I don't have any support. I'm just getting comfortable.
Maybe they're worried about how they look, how they stage, and so on.
I'd like to think that it's not that you're not filming, but what do you think?
I'm filming.
On the other hand, I wonder if I'm getting it right when I'm filming. I'm wondering if I'm doing it right when I'm filming.
I mean, I'm sure you'll look better after you're conscious of it.
Both of you?
Let's put aside for the moment the generation that wasn't photographed in detail in the first place.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think that even if there are a few people who are a bit of a don't-know-it-all type after the kids, they don't tend to be too busy.
Hmmm...
℃-ute bought the first half... the first half was appropriate...
Oda-chan, are you okay to read this? My heart.
That's not what I said! Please don't cut it out!
I stopped caring about it in the middle.I stopped caring about it in the middle.
Hmm.
Suzuki's always better when there's fewer people.
Are you skipping?
No, I'm not skipping. I'm just being really honest.
At the time, I felt like my body was in rhythm with the rhythm of the voice coming out of here.
And the rhythm of the voice coming out of here.
I felt like the 16 beats here weren't linked.
I could get it here, but I couldn't get it there.
I often felt that I could get it here, but not there.
My hand was cracked.
I see.
When it's in your body, you don't have to keep the rhythm with your body.
I just sat there the whole time.
I can feel the rhythm in your voice.
I'm sure it's going to be a pleasant song whether you're sitting or lying down.
I'm sure it will be a pleasant song.
But I haven't been able to see Suzuki's recent performance.
I'll take a good look next time.
Oh, man.
I can't control it.
I don't mean that.
I'm going to cry so hard!
Next is the lyrics presentation that touched my heart.Next up was the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
There are many lyrics in Hello!
Project has many lyrics that touch our hearts, but the lyrics of the new song of Morning Musume。 23's new song "Heavy Gate," which is included in the album I mentioned earlier.
Heavy Gate, a new song on the album that I mentioned earlier, has the word "loneliness garita" at the end of every chorus.
The word "solitary gharita" is at the end of every chorus of the song "Heavy Gate".
It's the kanji for "solitude" and the katakana for "garita",
I wondered what it means.
The members of Morning Musume。 We discussed it a lot with the members of Morning Musume,
We discussed it a lot with the members of Morning Musume,
After receiving your answer, I thought I would tell you now,
I was going to tell you now, but I think it's still time to think and enjoy, so I won't tell you yet.
Do you have any, Yua?
I am a member of Morning Musume。 18's
A is!
A-na!
by Morning Musume' 18.
I love the lyrics of this song, "Everything in life is your responsibility, don't be tied down by the past.
I always listen to it and get courage and energy from it.
A-na! It's amazing, isn't it?
It's a great song no matter where you take it, so please take a look at it.
Now please watch the VTR.
Go ahead!
Presentation of lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present lyrics from Hello! Project's songs that have touched our hearts and talk about their charms.
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project songs and talk about their charms.I hope that you, the viewers of Halo! I hope you, the readers of Halo!
I, Ruri Hiromoto, will be presenting this week.
This way! Jan!
It's a song called "Soto Hada wa Tropical Night" from Ojanoma's 2nd single,
The lyrics of the second verse, "It's not what you look like, it's what's on the inside that counts. The second lyric is about wanting to be praised all the way down to the tips of your toes,
Sumire Tashiro sings it for us,
Sumire Tashiro sings it, and it's really good.
It's really good.
I want people to look at my appearance, too.
I'm happy when people say how cute I am, but I also want them to see what's inside me,
But I also want them to see what's inside,
But I also want them to see what's inside, and I want to be praised for everything.
This is also true for idols,
When you like us,
Project, I want people to like us because of our performance,
That is what is inside of us. That's the essence of performance, isn't it?
I want you to like me because of my performance, but I also want you to like me because of my performance,
I want people to like me for my performance, but I also want them to say, "Nanami, you look cute today too,
It's a song about that kind of girl's maiden heart, and it's really good.
That's for sure. I really like the part about wanting to be praised all the way down to her toes,
The toes are the lowest part of the body,
I think the toes are the lowest part of the body, so it's a place that the human eye doesn't see very often,
I felt again that the lyrics are about a girl and about us, that we want to be praised until the very end.
It is also a lyric to tell girls that they are doing their best,It is also a lyric to convey that the girls are doing their best,
I think it is a part that makes us happy that you see a lot of us.
Please give it a listen.
Please look forward to the next installment!
Hallo! STE
Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda and Ria Matsunaga of Juice-Juice,
Ria Matsunaga of Juice-Juice will be presenting "Halo! Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year.
Project's 25th anniversary this year!
Project's 25th anniversary this year.
Project's 25 years of music videos.
Okay, first of all, I, Sakura Oda, have made my choice!
I, Sakura Oda, would like to share with you my choice for the most unique music video.
I'd like to show you with him!
Yes, this is a song by Morning Musume。 This is a song by Morning Musume。
The costumes are very unique and the members themselves are unique.
The members themselves at that time were very unique.
The ages of the members also varied.
They ranged from junior high school students to people in their 20s and even 25 years old.
Some looked like office workers, some were dressed like elementary school students.
Some were gals.
Some were maids.
There were police officers and so on.
But the coloring was just so unbelievable.
The parents' clothes were like, "What? I mean...
It's like, "How can you have that color in a uniform?It's like, there's no way you can have that shade in a uniform.
But it was a uniform color.
And they had these amazing headdresses and stuff.
I wondered what they would have guessed if I had been there.
It was a costume that really suited the person in question.
I wondered what it was because it was me.
I thought, "If I were the current Morning Musume。 If it were Morning Musume。
I enjoy imagining what everyone else would wear.
It's not a crazy life.
I think and act in my own way.
I love everyone in my family, but
I'm the generation that chases after love
I'm lonely, you know, and I'm a little worried
I'll call you, and yes, I'll be a little relieved
But I can't wait to see you again
I can't wait to see you
I love you so much, you know, I'm a little nervous
I kiss you and... well, that's quite a kiss.
I'm still a little nervous
Love is hard
Hello! Ste!
Yes, and I, Riai Matsunaga, have chosen a unique music video
Love Dance Site.
Yes, I also chose it from Morning Musume。 This song has a very unique sound, doesn't it?
This song has a very unique sound, doesn't it?This song has a very unique sound.
The song itself is very unique, and the chorus is also very unique.
The video also has a very unique feel that is completely different from what we see today.
Especially when we shot the close-up lip scene.
It was so close in the old days.
It's so close.
The dance scene, the changeover, the costumes, and so on.
Everything is so unique.
I hope you will pay attention to all of them and listen to the music.
Whenever I fall in love, I play pom-pom-pom with my chest.
Every time you kiss, yada-pon-pa-pon
With each good and gentle heart
Even if you are messing around
Right, the homepage of my life
I'll update it with a sexy beam
Let's laugh, let's love, let's love, I've got to see you again
Wai-ya-ya-ya, ah-ya-ya, at full volume
Ribbons in the air of love
Good job, good job, good job
Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda and
Ria Matsunaga of Juice-Juice is presenting the Halo! Stay!
It's time to say goodbye!
Here is an announcement!
Hello Project 2023 Summer City Circuit is now underway!
Morning Musume。 23 will perform in Hiroshima on August 11!Morning Musume。' 23 will perform in Hiroshima on August 11
Juice-Juice will perform in Shinjuku on August 19.
We are looking forward to it!
We will do our best!
And on August 13, we will perform at Rock in Japan Festival 2023!
From Hello Project, Morning Musume. 23, Angulum and Juice-Juice will perform!
It is an outdoor festival, so I will enjoy it as much as I do in summer!
We will do our best!
And Morning Musume。 23 will perform at the Morning Musume。 Best Selection
THE 25th Anniversary album.
I told you a little bit about this album in the main program.
As I mentioned a little bit in the main program, we have selected various songs from the 25th anniversary and re-sung them by the current members, as well as new songs.
I hope you will check it out.
In addition, Morning Musume。 23 will also be going on an autumn tour!
The tour will start on September 16th at Harmony Hall Zama Ogawakiri.
This will be the first tour since the new members joined the group.
In addition, it is also the graduation tour of our leader, Sei Fukumura.
We hope that many of you will come to see us!
Thank you very much for your support.
Yes, Juice-Juice will also be going on an autumn tour.
Please watch over us as we continue to move forward in our 10th anniversary year!
And on September 9 and 10, we will be performing at the National Stadium 1st Gymnasium.
Hello Project 25th Anniversary Concert will be held on September 9 and 10 at the National Stadium 1st Gymnasium.
This is a festival, isn't it?
Yes, as the title suggests, we will be holding a concert to commemorate the 25th anniversary of Hello Project.Yes, as the title says, we are celebrating our 25th anniversary.
We are very much looking forward to this concert.
We are very much looking forward to this concert, so please come and enjoy it!
The audition for the new members of Hello Project 25th Anniversary is due on August 14!
We are really looking forward to the day when we can sing together!